{
    "a":
    [{
        "question":"Which of the following is the most secure protocol to use when accessing a wireless network?",
        "answers":["WEP","WPA","WPA2","TKIP"],
        "correct":2 
    },
    {
        "question":"What should you configure to improve wireless security?",
        "answers":["Enable the SSID","IP Spoofing","Remove repeaters","MAC filtering"],
        "correct":3 
    },
    {
        "question":"In a wireless network, why is an SSID used?",
        "answers":["To secure the wireless access point","To identify the network","To encrypt data","To enforce Mac filtering"],
        "correct":1 
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the most common problem associated with UTP cable?",
        "answers":["Crosstalk","Data emanation","Chromation dispersion","Vampire tapping"],
        "correct":0 
    },
    {
        "question":"What two security precautions can best help to protect against wireless network attacks?",
        "answers":["Authentication and Wep","Access Control Lists and WEP","Identification and WPA2","Authentication and WPA"],
        "correct":3 
    }],

    "b":
    [{
        "question":"Which of the following, when removed, can increase the security of a wireless access point?",
        "answers":["Mac filtering","SSID","WPA","Firewall"],
        "correct":1 
    },
    {
        "question":"A wireless network switch has connectivity issues but only when the air-conditioning system is running. What can be added to fix the problem?",
        "answers":["Shielding","A wireless network","A key deflector","Redundant air-conditioning system"],
        "correct":0 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is the most secure type of cabling?",
        "answers":["Unshielded twisted-pair","Shielded twisted-pair","Coaxial","Category 6"],
        "correct":1 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is the least secure type of wireless encryption?",
        "answers":["WEP 64-bit","WEP 128-bit","WPA with TKIP","WPA2 with AES"],
        "correct":0 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is the unauthorized access of information from a Bluetooth device?",
        "answers":["Bluejacking","Bluesnarfing","Deep Blue","The Blues Brothers"],
        "correct":1 
    }],

    "c":
    [{
        "question":"Which of the following can be described as the act of exploiting a bug or flaw in software to gain access to resources that normally would be portected?",
        "answers":["Privilege escalation","Chain of custody","Default account","Backdoor"],
        "correct":0 
    },
    {
        "question":"You scan your network and find a rogue AP with the same SSID used by your network. What type of attack is occuring?",
        "answers":["War-driving","Bluesnarfing","Evil twin","IV attack"],
        "correct":2 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is an unauthorized wireless router that allows access to a secure router?",
        "answers":["Rogue AP","Evil twin","War-driving","AP isolation"],
        "correct":0 
    },
    {
        "question":"Your boss asks you to limit the wireless signal of a WAP from going outside the building. What should you do?",
        "answers":["Put the atenna on the exterior of the building","Disable the SSID","Enable MAC filtering","Decreate the poewer levels of the WAP"],
        "correct":3 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following should be considered to mitigate data theft when using Cat 6 wiring?",
        "answers":["Multimode fiber","EMI shielding","CCTV","Passive scanning"],
        "correct":1 
    }]
}
